Guide to the Richard Minsky Archive
Yale University Arts Library
Richard Minsky archive
1960-2014
AOB 8
Yale University Arts Library
35
(74 boxes + flat files)
The Richard Minsky Archive contains correspondence, personal papers, photographs, artwork, publications, and ephemera that document his career as well as shed light on the history of book arts in New York City.
Minsky, Richard, 1947-
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of Richard Minsky, 2004-.
Associated Materials
Interviews with book artist Richard Minsky (digital collection), Robert B. Haas Family Arts Library, Yale University.
Conditions Governing Access
Boxes 57, 68, and 69 ( SLART documentation) are restricted until Minsky's death.
Boxes 44, 45, 58-74 are closed for processing and require curatorial permission before use.
Biographical / Historical
Richard Minsky, pioneering contemporary book artist and founder of the Center for Book Arts in New York City, is known for his conceptual approach to hand bookbinding and commitment to changing the perception of the book arts from craft to fine art. Based in New York, Minsky is noted for his interest in the economics of art and his innovative use of an age-old tradition and new materials to create sculptural, often political bookworks. His blending of an eclectic mix of interests, from musical and theatre performance to social issues and virtual worlds, remain a hallmark of Minsky's career.
Richard Philip Minsky was born January 7, 1947, in New York, NY. From the age of 13, he operated a letterpress printshop out of his home in Queens. As a teenager his diverse interests also included photography, vocal and violin music performance, and astronomy. He attended Brooklyn College from 1964-68 and earned a MA in Economics from Brown University in 1969. At Brown he met Daniel Gibson Knowlton, the University Bookbinder, who mentored Minsky in an independent study program of hand bookbinding and repair. He subsequently attended the New School for Social Research, and during this time he became a binder and photographer at the Hirshhorn Museum. It was while working with art at the Hirshhorn, says Minsky, that he was inspired to create his first binding intended to be an art object in 1971. He decided to pursue that career path and shortly afterward opened a hand bookbindery, printshop, and art gallery in Forest Hills, Queens. Minsky devoted himself to creating books that function as sculptural metaphors for the contents within – an approach he has described as "material as metaphor."
In 1974, with the goal of advancing and promoting the book arts, he established the Center for Book Arts (CBA) at 15 Bleecker Street in Manhattan and moved his bookbinding facility there. He continued to explore his musical and theatrical interests, creating hybrid media works like Adventures in Ku-ta-ba Wa-do (1974), for which he composed and performed music, as well as created and printing images based on poetry. Minsky taught at the School of Visual Arts in Manhattan (1977-78) and began lecturing extensively on his projects and the book arts at institutions in England and New York throughout the next three decades. He was awarded five successive years of NEA grants which funded an apprenticeship program at the CBA and opportunities for him to travel abroad. He also went to England as a US/UK Bicentennial Fellow at the Camberwell School of Art and Crafts in 1978-79, producing the book Minsky in London as a result. In addition to his collaborative projects with artists and writers such as Tom Phillips and Jonathan Williams, Minsky successfully undertook many private commissions, including the register for the New York City Mayor's residence Gracie Mansion. He remained active with the Center for Book Arts, serving in a variety of roles.
In 1990 he organized the national conference "Book Arts in the USA", which brought together 400 regional book arts administrators and artists, and curated an exhibition of 51 bookworks that traveled abroad as a Cultural Presentation of the United States through the Arts America program of the United States Information Agency. From 1993-2001 Minsky created one of his best known bodies of work, a Bill of Rights-themed series of ten pieces that address the meaning of each amendment. His choice of socially and politically themed books that relate to the amendments resulted in bookworks that are responsive, topical, and reflective of his own beliefs. During this time he also participated in solo and group exhibitions and curated shows of other artists, while continuing to write and lecture on the book arts and economics. As computer and printing technology evolved, so did Minsky, who pioneered a method of inkjet printing to produce books and broadsides on handmade paper from Dieu Donné Papermill. He also explored online virtual worlds by creating a presence in Second Life to curate and critique virtual art. From 2006-2010, Minsky collected, researched and exhibited American publisher's bindings and published three volumes on the subject, as well as a trade edition.
Scope and Contents
The Richard Minsky archive contains correspondence, personal papers, photographs, artwork, publications, and ephemera that document his career as well as shed light on the history of book arts in New York City. Examples of Minsky's music are in the collection in the form of reel-to-reel tapes and sheet music. Minsky's personal and collaborative projects are well-represented through sketches, printing plates, leather samples, photographs of in-process and completed work, color and technique tests, and layout mock-ups.
Arrangement
Organized into five series + oversize: Series I. Biographical, 1960-2009. Series II. Personal Correspondence, 1964-2003. Series III. Business Files & Correspondence, 1960-2004. Series IV. Project Files, 1968-2010. Series V. Interviews with Richard Minsky, 2014. Oversize, 1969-2010.
Later additions date from 2011, 2012, 2013, and 2014.
Artists' books -- United States; Minsky, Richard, 1947-
- Biographical, 1960-2009; Series I
  Scope and Contents
  This series begins with Photos, which contains images of Minsky and book artists such as Tom Phillips, Dikko Faust, Joni Mabe, and others. Early examples of his photography are found here in the form of his 1960s negative files. Pre-College covers Minsky's early school years, from elementary through high school, and contains ephemera such as aptitude tests, certificates of merit, early photography and contributions to the Richmond Hill High School paper, The Domino. Junior Astronomy Club activities from this time, including photos and newsletters, are located under "Biographical - Other Interests." Of special note in that section is a fake press pass (for Junior Astronomy Club News) that Minsky printed to photograph President Lyndon B. Johnson during a visit to New York. College documents are comprised of economics papers and acceptance and scholarship letters, as well as a certificate from Brown for completing Daniel Knowlton's hand bookbinding course in 1969. One of the largest sections in this series is Exhibition Announcements & Media Coverage. These folders are arranged by date. Articles about Minsky, announcements or coverage of his shows, and VHS tapes of television appearances are located here. Book Arts Ephemera includes material collected by Minsky documenting the book arts such as catalogs for Book Arts programs, exhibitions, and small press sales. Book Arts Organizations folders present an overview of the organizations that Minsky was a part of throughout his career, primarily the Center for Book Arts. Newsletters and ephemera are included. Art Events folders contain postcards and flyers from shows that Minsky attended or received notice of, spanning the 70s through the present. There are also various works that he collected for himself, including parts of the Tom Phillips book A Humument, under Work By Others.
  - Photos, 1960s-2000s (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
    - Negative File A-E, 1960s (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Negative File D-K, 1960s (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Negative File L-S, 1960s (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Negative File T-Z, 1960s (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Scholastic Arts Writing Awards, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Pre-College, 1960s (Box 2, Folder 8-9)
  - College, 1960s-1970s (Box 2, Folder 10)
    See also Series V for Minsky's discussion of his bookbinding course materials from Brown University.
    - Economics, 1960s-1970s (Box 2, Folder 11-12)
    - Economics, 1960s-1970s (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Travel Documents, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Exhibition Announcements & Media Coverage, 1969-1974 1974-1977 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 15-18)
    See also Series V for Minsky's discussion of his 1974 Zabriskie Gallery show; the 1975 Guild of Book Workers show held in the Arts of the Book Room at Yale's Sterling Memorial Library; his 1977 NEA Craftsman Fellowship award; and an American Crafts in the White House brochure.
    See also: Oversize, box 47, folder 139.
  - Exhibition Announcements & Media Coverage, 1981 1982-1984 1985-1989 (Box 4, Folder 19-24)
    See also Series V for Minsky's discussion of the schematic for his 1981 show at Allan Stone Gallery.
    General note
    See also: Oversize, box 43, folder 132; and Oversize, box 47, folder 139.
  - Exhibition Announcements & Media Coverage, 1990-1992 (Box 5, Folder 25-29)
    See also: Oversize, box 43, folder 132.
    - Harper Collins 25-Year Retrospective, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Exhibition Announcements & Media Coverage, 1993-2009 (Folder 6, Folder 31-36)
  - Exhibition Announcements & Media Coverage, undated (Box 7, Folder 37)
    - VHS Tapes, 1980-1986 1998-2001 (Box 7, Folder 38-39)
  - Conferences and Lectures, 1979-1995 2001-2008 (Box 7, Folder 40-41)
    See also: Oversize, box 47, folder 135.
    - Book Arts in the USA, 1989-1990 (Box 8, Folder 42-44)
    - Scholastic Art & Writing Awards, 2000 (Box 9, Folder 45)
    - I.D. Badges, 1990-2009 (Box 9, Folder 46)
  - Book Arts Ephemera (Box 9)
    - 1970s (Box 9, Folder 47)
    - 1980s, 1980-1987 (Box 9, Folder 48-49)
    - 1980s, 1987-1989 (Box 10, Folder 50-51)
    - 1990s, 1990-1996 (Box 10, Folder 52-54)
    - 2000s, 2000-2008 (Box 10, Folder 55)
    - undated (Box 11, Folder 56)
  - Book Arts Organizations (Box 11)
    - Franklin Furnace, 1980-2002 (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - Guild of Book Workers, 1975-1984 1990-2003 (Box 11, Folder 58-59)
    - Minnesota Center for Book Arts, 1987-2003 (Box 11, Folder 60)
    - Center for Book Arts (Box 12)
      - 1970s, 1974-1979 (Box 12, Folder 61-62)
        See also Series V for Minsky's discussion of the invitation to the opening exhibition at CBA; the Center's Bleecker Street stationery; and a draft press release announcing Minsky's resignation at CBA after accepting a UK/US Bicentennial Fellowship.
      - 1980s, 1980-1981 (Box 12, Folder 63-64)
      - 1980s, 1982 1984-1989 (Box 13, Folder 65-67)
      - 1990s, 1990-1991 (Box 13, Folder 68-69)
        See also Series V for Minsky's discussion of the letterhead for Book Arts in the USA, 1st National Conference.
      - 1990s, 1992-1993 1995-1999 (Box 14, Folder 70-72)
      - 2000s, 2000-2004 (Box 14, Folder 73)
      - undated (Box 14, Folder 74)
    - Dieu Donné, 1981-2004 (Box 14, Folder 75)
    - Other, 1970s-2000s (Box 15, Folder 76-77)
  - Other Interests (Box 15)
    - Art Events 1960s, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 78)
    - Art Events 1970s, 1970-1979 (Box 15, Folder 79-80)
    - Art Events 1980s, 1980-1989 (Box 15, Folder 81-82)
    - Art Events 1990s, 1990-1999 (Box 16, Folder 83-87)
    - Art Events 2000s, 2000-2009 (Box 17, Folder 88-90)
    - Art Events undated (Box 17, Folder 91)
    - Boating, 1977-1990 (Box 17, Folder 92)
    - Junior Astronomy Club, 1960s (Box 17, Folder 93)
      See also: Oversize, box 43, folder 131.
    - Junior Astronomy Club, 1960s (Box 18, Folder 94-96)
      See also Series V for Minsky's discussion of his Junior Astronomy Club press pass.
    - Music & Theatre Performances, 1967-1974 (Box 18, Folder 97)
    - Music & Theatre Performances, 1980-1993 (Box 19, Folder 98)
    - Music & Theatre Performances, undated (Box 19, Folder 99)
      See also: Oversize, box 43, folder 134.
    - Music & Theatre Performances audio tapes (Box 55)
      Also includes Adventures in Ku-ta-ba Wa-do recordings.
    - Tango, 1980-1990 (Box 19, Folder 100)
  - Work By Others, 1973-1993 (Box 19, Folder 101-102)
  - Work By Others, 1994-2001 undated (Box 20, Folder 103-104)
    - A Humument, undated (Box 20, Folder 105)
- Personal Correspondence, 1964-2003; Series II
  Personal correspondence contains letters, cards, and other correspondence between Minsky and his friends, family, other artists, and colleagues. Included are holiday cards from book dealers and friends. Of note is the letter sent by President Lyndon B. Johnson's social secretary, thanking Minsky for sending a photo that he took of the President.
  - 1960s-1970s, 1964-1979 (Box 20, Folder 106)
  - 1980s, 1980-1982 (Box 20, Folder 107)
  - 1980s, 1982-1989 (Box 21, Folder 108-109)
  - 1990s (Box 21, Folder 110-111)
  - 1990s, 1991-1998 (Box 22, Folder 112)
  - 2000s, 2000-2007 (Box 22, Folder 113)
  - undated (Box 22, Folder 114)
  - Holiday Cards, 1975-2003 undated (Box 22, Folder 115-116)
- Business Files & Correspondence, 1960-2004; Series III
  This series contains business correspondence, legal & financial documents, and general business files. These folders are arranged by date, and contain invoices for materials purchased by Minsky as well as invoices he sent to others for his work. There are also tax forms, accounting ephemera such as ledgers and alphabetical files, and miscellaneous legal/financial documents. SLART legal documents are here as well, but this material is restricted until Minsky's death. The general business files section contains miscellaneous papers related to Minsky's day-to-day business operations. Of particular interest is a book of Minsky's printing samples from the 1960s, which he used to show off his work and generate new business.
  - Correspondence, 1960s 1970-1991 (Box 23, Folder 117-122)
    See also Series V for Minsky's discussion of a letter regarding the incorporation of the Center for Book Arts (CBA) and also a memo from Judith Hoffberg.
  - Correspondence, 1992-1994 (Box 24, Folder 123)
    - Encyclopedia of Publishing & The Book Arts, 1993 (Box 24, Folder 124)
    - MCBA/Grosbard/Geography Of Hunger, 1994 (Box 24, Folder 125)
  - Correspondence, 1995-1999 2000s undated (Box 24, Folder 126-128)
  - Legal & Financial Documents, 1970-1974 (Box 24, Folder 129)
    See also Minsky's discussion of an invoice that includes Pettigrew's History of Egyptian Mummies among other items.
  - Legal & Financial Documents, 1970-1979 (Box 25, Folder 130-131)
  - Legal & Financial Documents, 1978 (Box 25, Folder 132)
  - Legal & Financial Documents, 1980-1989 (Box 25, Folder 133-134)
    - Glick Bookbinding Project, 1980 (Box 25, Folder 135)
  - Legal & Financial Documents, 1990 (Box 25, Folder 136)
  - Legal & Financial Documents, 1991-1997 (Box 26, Folder 137-140)
    - Accounts Binder, 2000 (Box 26, Folder 141)
    - Other Artists' Work Samples, 1960-1990 (Box 27, Folder 142)
    - SLART, circa 2000s (Box 57)
      Conditions Governing Access
      Boxes 57, 68, and 69 are restricted until Minsky's death.
  - Legal & Financial Documents, undated (Box 27, Folder 143)
  - General Business Files, 1968-1989 (Box 27, Folder 144-146)
  - General Business Files, 1990-2004 (Box 28, Folder 147)
    - Rose Slivka Lecture Tour, 1994 (Box 28, Folder 148)
    - Minsky on CD, 2001 (Box 28, Folder 149)
  - General Business Files, undated (Box 28, Folder 150-151)
  - General Business Files, undated (Box 29, Folder 152)
    - Resumes, 1960s-1990s (Box 29, Folder 153)
    - Grant Applications, 1970s-1990s (Box 29, Folder 154)
    - Printing Examples & Printing Book, 1960s (Box 29, Folder 155)
      See also Series V for Minsky's discussion of his early business card and printing samples.
    - Bookbinding and Repairing Kit, 1974 (Box 30, Folder 156)
  - Legal & Financial Documents – Alphabetical Files, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 157)
  - Legal & Financial Documents – Alphabetical Files, 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 158)
  - Legal & Financial Documents – Student Receipts, 1972-1973 (Box 30, Folder 159)
  - Legal & Financial Documents – Alphabetical Files, 1974 (Box 31, Folder 160)
  - Legal & Financial Documents – Ledger, 1972-1974 (Box 31, Folder 161)
- Project Files, 1968-2010; Series IV
  Project Files contain materials produced in the creation of Minsky's art. Project files include process materials such as sketches, printing plates, leather samples, photographs of in-process and completed work, color and technique tests, wax maquettes and latex molds, and layout mock-ups. Of particular interest are files containing casting molds for projects (such as the Grosbard Bar Mitzvah or Chateau Vervaines Guestbook. There are several files that show many states of a project from beginning to end: Minsky in Bed, Minsky in London, the Chateau Vervaines Guestbook, and the American Decorated Publisher's Bindings books are good examples of this. Of note is also the Buckminster Fuller Tetrascroll project, which includes a small handmade journal containing handwritten notes on the process of construction and thoughts about the process. Adventures in Ku-Ta-Ba Wa-Do files include reel-to-reel tapes of Minsky's music that was composed for the project, in various stages of mix-down. Minsky's career included many guestbooks and other commissioned works; they can be found under the subset of Private Commissions. These are grouped together by title or the client's last name, if no other title was given. They are organized by date of creation and contain applicable correspondence about that project in addition to the process materials.
  Arrangement
  Please note that folder numbering restarts with this series.
  - The Book, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 1)
  - The Georgics of Virgil, 1969 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Blank Book, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Diary, 1971 (Box 32, Folder 4)
  - Diary, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Prométhée, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    See also: Oversize, box 47, folder 136.
  - Adventures in Ku-ta-ba Wa-do, 1973 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    In addition to the project files, the Adventures in Ku-ta-ba Wa-do album and music booklet are individually cataloged in Orbis.
  - Adventures in Ku-ta-ba Wa-do original & master recordings (Box 52)
    See also: box 55.
  - Box for La Tentation de St. Antoine, circa 1970s (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Det Norske Folkes Rebinding, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - Stamping dies, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Birds of North America, 1975 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    See also: Oversize, box 50, folder 148.
  - Buckminster Fuller's Tetrascroll, 1976-1977 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Buckminster Fuller's Tetrascroll, 1976-1977 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - Journal, 1976-1977 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - Correspondence, 1976-1977 (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - The Dog Bite, 1977 (Box 32, Folder 16)
  - Babel, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 17)
  - Blank Book for Dante's Inferno, 1979 (Box 32, Folder 18)
  - Achieving Ecstasy During the Apocalypse, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 19)
  - The Crisis of Democracy, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 20)
  - Minsky in London, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    See also: Oversize, box 43, folder 133; Oversize, box 49, folder 146; Oversize, box 50, folder 148; Oversize, box 53, folder 149.
    - Correspondence, 1979-1980 (Box 32, Folder 22)
  - Be Minsky, 1980 (Box 32, Folder 23)
  - Benzene Ad: "Talk Too Much?", 1981 (Box 32, Folder 24)
  - Immortal Dreamers, 1981-1982 (Box 32, Folder 25)
  - Minsky Finances Inc., 1984 (Box 32, Folder 26)
  - Seventy Studies, 1985 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Roseland Ballroom Restoration, 1985-1986 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Dante's Inferno VHS, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - There's a Pig in the Sky, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - There's a Pig in the Sky, 1986 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - The Heart of A Humument, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - 32 Studies, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Laying Waste, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - Warhol Bugatti Chair Restoration, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - Correspondence, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - Missile Envy, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - Tragedy and Hope, 1988 (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - Minsky in Bed, 1989-1992 (Box 33, Folder 39)
    See also: Oversize, box 47, folder 137; Oversize, box 46, folder 140; Oversize, box 46, folder 141; Oversize, box 53, folder 149.
  - Minsky in Bed, 1989-1992 (Box 34, Folder 40)
    See also Series V for Minsky's discussion of proofs for Minsky in Bed.
  - Minsky in Bed, 1989-1992 (Box 34, Folder 41)
    See also Series V for Minsky's discussion of a draft colophon for Minsky in Bed.
  - Minsky in Bed, 1989-1992 (Box 34, Folder 42)
    See also Series V for Minsky's discussion of manuscript drafts and chapter headings for Minsky in Bed.
  - Minsky in Bed, 1989-1992 (Box 34, Folder 43)
  - Minsky in Bed, 1989-1992 (Box 34, Folder 44)
  - Minsky in Bed, 1989-1992 (Box 34, Folder 45)
    - Correspondence, 1990-1996 (Box 35, Folder 46)
  - Plain Talk, 1989 (Box 35, Folder 47)
  - Holy Terror (Fundamentalist), 1988 (Box 35, Folder 48)
  - Holy Terror (Warhol), 1990 (Box 35, Folder 49)
  - Where Are They Now? (Class of '47), 1990 (Box 35, Folder 50)
  - Where Are They Now? (Class of '47), 1990 (Box 35, Folder 51)
    - Correspondence, 1990-1991 (Box 35, Folder 52)
  - Dreaming the Caves, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 53)
    See also: Oversize, box 47, folder 138.
    - Correspondence, 1991 (Box 35, Folder 54)
  - Fem Fatale, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 55)
  - Fem Fatale, 1992 (Box 35, Folder 56)
    - Correspondence, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 57)
  - Anathema Maranatha, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 58)
    - Correspondence, 1991-1993 (Box 36, Folder 59)
  - Becoming Light – Erica Jong, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 60)
    - Printing Plates, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 61)
  - The Geography of Hunger, 1992 (Box 36, Folder 62)
  - Animal Magnetism, 1992-1993 (Box 36, Folder 63)
    See also: Oversize, box 47, folder 138; Oversize, box 50, folder 148.
  - 1st Amendment (Book Burning Kit), 1993 (Box 36, Folder 64)
  - The Bill of Rights Series, 1993-2002 (Box 36, Folder 65)
    See also: Oversize, box 43, folder 127; Oversize, box 43, folder 128; Oversize, box 43, folder 129.
  - The Eye, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 66)
    - Correspondence, 1994 (Box 36, Folder 67)
  - Boston Blackie in Paris, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 68)
    - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 36, Folder 69)
  - Inventing Memory - Erica Jong, 1998 (Box 36, Folder 70)
  - The Philosophy of Umbrellas, 2007 (Box 36, Folder 71)
    - Correspondence, 2007-2008 (Box 36, Folder 72)
  - American Decorated Publishers' Bindings vol.1, 2006 (Box 36, Folder 73)
    See also: Oversize, box 47, folder 142; Oversize, box 47, folder 143.
  - American Decorated Publishers' Bindings 1872-1929, vol.1, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 74)
  - American Decorated Publishers' Bindings 1872-1929, vol.1, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 75)
    - Cover Plate Stamp, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 76)
    - Cover Plate Stamp, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 77)
  - American Decorated Publishers' Bindings 1872-1929, vol.2, 2009 (Box 37, Folder 78)
  - American Decorated Publishers' Bindings 1872-1929, vol.2, 2009 (Box 37, Folder 79)
  - American Decorated Publishers' Bindings 1872-1929, vol.2, 2009 (Box 37, Folder 80)
  - American Decorated Publishers' Bindings 1872-1929, vol.2, 2009 (Box 38, Folder 81)
    - CD, 2009 (Box 38, Folder 82)
    - Stamp for Spine, 2009 (Box 38, Folder 83)
  - Freedom of Choice, 2009 (Box 38, Folder 84)
  - The Art of American Book Covers, 1875-1930, 2010 (Box 38, Folder 85)
    See also: Oversize, box 47, folder 143.
  - Crimes of Compassion, undated (Box 38, Folder 86)
  - The Drawings of Eugene Delacroix, undated (Box 38, Folder 87)
  - Hagenauer Wein, undated (Box 38, Folder 88)
  - La Sexualite – Latex Mold, undated (Box 38, Folder 89)